A Guide to the United Way of Greater Richmond /Richmond Community records 1911-1987
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Young Volunteers in Action-Advisory Council 1982 (Box 47)
- Young Volunteers in Action-Letter of Invitation 1982 (Box 47)
- Young Volunteers in Action-Newsletter 1982 (Box 47)
- Young Volunteers in Action-Newsletter and Information 1982 (Box 47)
- Young Volunteers in Action-Slides 1982 (Box 47)
- Young Volunteers in Action-Staff Agenda 1982 (Box 47)
- Presidential Photographs of the Richmond Community Council 1911-1974 (Box 47)
- Other Photographs (Box 47)
- Rental Properties for the Richmond Community Fund (Box 48)
- Scrapbook 1938 (Box 1)
- Scrapbook 1935-1936 (Box 2)
- Scrapbook 1956, 1961, 2 scrapbooks (Box 3)
- Scrapbook 1934 (Box 5)
- Scrapbook 1953 (Box 6)
- Scrapbook 1936 (Box 7)
- Scrapbook 1952-1957 (Box 8)
- Scrapbook 1959-1965 (Box 9)
- Scrapbook 1935 (Box 10)
- Scrapbook 1938, 1943 (Box 11)
- Scrapbook 1943 (Box 12)
- Scrapbook 1950, 1944 (Box 13)
- Scrapbook 1941 (Box 14)
- Scrapbook, United Giver's Fund 1967 (Box 15)
- Scrapbook 1966-1967 (Box 16)
- Loose Clippings 1960s-1970s (Box 16)
- Scrapbook 1951 (Box 17)
- Scrapbook 1944-1946 (Box 18)
- Scrapbook 1941-1943 (Box 19)
- Volunteer Service Bureau (Box 19)
- Scrapbook 1941 (Box 20)
- Campaign Book 1940 (Box 20)
- Scrapbook 1937-1938 (Box 21)
- Campaign Book 1935 (Box 21)
- Richmond Christmas Mother's Fund (Box 22)
- Scrapbook 1942 (Box 22)
- Scrapbook 1952 (Box 24)
- Scrapbook 1920s-1930s (Box 24)
- Scrapbook 1968-1969 (Box 25)
- Scrapbook 1970 (Box 26)